[Praise]
Satyam is also present with us and
we have called Satyam today for some more data.
Look, there is an atmosphere of fear everywhere in the market
that everything is falling, everything is breaking, the
market is becoming very weak. So,
first I will present some data before you,
then we will
discuss more data related to Satyam in the market.
Sir, if we look at today's situation, the
valuation discomfort that was there seems to be moving towards some
comfort. If we
look at the 10-year average numbers, then Nifty, Midcap, Small Cap,
Sensex, all of these seem to be in better shape and
coming into better situation. For
example, if we talk about Nifty, the
current multiple of Nifty is
around 18.5. The 10-year average is 18.5,
so almost we are around that.
Sensex is 19.3, its average multiple for 10
years is 19.09. Currently, the Sensex is functioning.
Mid cap is trading at an average multiple of 24 in 10 years,
right now we are standing at 245, as soon as it
comes down slightly, mid cap will also become comfortable
and small cap has an average multiple of 19,
we are standing at 21, so a little steam
is left there too, but large cap has
come into comfort, mid cap has
come into slightly comfort and small cap
is slightly overvalued, but now let's
talk about this stock specific, from the
stock, go through the list of SHAR AAC 500
and find out those shares in it which are
either below the 10 year average or let's say
that they have come below the average price of Covid,
so Shaur ji, please start with the list,
tell me, yes sir, you are absolutely right that to a
large extent the valuation concerns
seem to be ending and the companies that I have brought, they have
now come below their valuation of the time of Covid, if
we compare, then let's start this
list from the top  First, Bajaj will be trapped in this,
whose PE ratio at the time of Covid on March 2, 2020,
was 51.4, now its PE multiple is
36.6, so its valuation has come down even below its Covid level.
As per PE, Maruti.com
was at 39.2, now it has come down to PE of 28.9.
Sorry, I missed the name of Satyam,
Samm Shor said it while being lazy,
but these four names are on your screen,
Bajaj's, Coal India and Inter Globe Aviation,
see Rachit Sir, out of these four names, all these
four have now gone to the attractive side,
but if someone wants to
go with comfort because there is
no concern about their quality, then all of them are now
big names of the country, it is the largest NBFC, the
largest four-wheeler, Coal
India, the world's coal producer and the
country's largest aviation company, the
valuations of all these four have become cheap, now if
someone wants to pick from these four then
According to you, which one looks better,
sir, see in this, if I tell you a
very simple advice, it would be that in these four
you should deploy your fund at 25:25,
you will also get to see the diversity
and you will get the best of all the
industries which are working, that is, if
we talk about Inter Globe Aviation,
its market share is 64, Coal India is the
world's largest coal producer, if you
want long term stable growth and good dividend payment, then Mati
suzuki.com,
its high valuation was being talked about,
so it is improving to a great extent, the next
company is BPCL which was at a PE of 12.5,
now it is working at a PE of 7.1,
Indus Tower's name is also there in this, its valuation has decreased from PE of 23.2,
its PE is now 88.9,
PE multiple of almost nine is of
BPCL Indust Hour and the next company is
III Lord which was at 47.8 PE at the
time of Covid  At present, it is trading at a PE multiple of 33.7.
We have these four names in front of you. The
country's and the world's second largest
aluminium company, Dalco, is trading at a multiple of 23,
BPCL at a multiple of seven, Indus Towers
at a multiple of nine and ICC Lombard
is trading at a multiple of around 34.
This valuation is in comparison to their pre-Covid valuations.
So, Rachit Sir, do
any names from this second list seem right?
Sir, I am not very confident
because you see,
BPCL has its own reasons. Dalco
is one of the world's largest mining companies, but the way the tariff drama is
going on, I am also apprehensive about that.
Indus Towers is definitely a name in
which you can make some interest.
And ICSC Lord Sir, you must have
seen that there is talk of an
announcement from the government that if
you buy general insurance or something like that
and if you do not understand it, then you can
ask for your premium back for one year.  Which may be a
bit debt-ridden for them,
so just to keep you a little distance from this,
I would like to tell you that
Rach Sir has already given his opinion on these four as well. Yes, Satyam is the
third name. Let's start the last list of
four companies. There are also ADAC AMC. The
first company in this is its PE
multiple of 50.4 at the time of Covid, which has
now fallen to 34.2. Then the next company is
ABOUT India, which
is currently trading at a multiple of 47.5 after decreasing from a multiple of 50.
Next is Oye Realty, where the
multiple was 56.7 at the time of Covid, now it has come down to 26.8,
so it is also available at a very low price. Next
is PI Industries, where its PE multiple has decreased from 44.9 at the
time of Covid and is currently
25.1. PI Industries is currently operating at a PE multiple of around 25.
So Rach
is diversified from mutual fund industry, from
pharma, from realty, from chemicals.
What should be done here, see HDFC AMC. So
now you have a little more problem.
If the problem in the market
increases, then we all know about it. It is only from 55 to
47.5. It is not a very amazing
correction that we are seeing, what other
things we are seeing, we are getting over a
reality. In the part of the
country that it serves, we are just seeing how the
demand is good there and it has
also been corrected. You can keep an eye on it here
and behind PI Industries,
you can see that the talks going on in chemicals
that the tariff for metals can become a problem, the
same can become a boon for chemicals.
If a
tariff is imposed on Chinese chemicals by the US,
our industry can also benefit from it,
so according to your position, you can make a call
bet on reality or PI
Industries. We, O'Bry and PI are two such
names which are looking comparatively better,
but this list has been presented before you so that it is
not that everything is
going bad in the market and the market is going bad.
Nothing is going well, many
things have become cheaper than before
and this cheapness means that it is
not visible only to you, it is visible to mutual funds
as well, it is visible to FIs as well,
so gradually we will come back, only such
companies will be identified first
where the valuation is better than before,
so if you have these shares then do
not worry, good companies have come at cheap prices, it may
take some time but they will come back easily
and shortly, thank you very much
Satyam for being with us today, for
sharing all the data with us and
for talking to us on these numbers
[appreciation]